I've met plenty of people who turned out
to be nice once I talked to them.
People often said I was hard to approach.
I'm terrible at starting conversations.
I'm glad we can talk about manga together.
It's been boring
because there's no one I click with.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Don't mention it.
If the environment is partly to blame
for the isolation,
I would…
HAMBURGER BOM BOM
Yeah. Then, this guy…
Amamiya? You listening?
'Course I am.
Oh, well.
EPISODE 2
LOCKSMITH
Join us for a good time.
No, thanks!
What do I even do?
TWO AGAINST ONE
WHAT IF I UPSET THEM
I'm terrified and angry.
THEY'RE MOCKING ME
WHAT A WASTE OF TIME
- How frustrating.
- Let's go.
- Come with us.
- It's gonna be fun.
I said I'm not interested!
I'm serious. Leave me alone.
Bye.
Sorry. You okay?
I thought it was you.
Mr. Giraffe?
I HAVE TO TAKE THE CROSSWALK
OVER THERE TO GET TO THIS SIDE
Sorry I ignored you back there.
Please pretend like we're friends.
I'm sorry,
but please stay with me
until we're out of their sight.
Say what?
I was able to meet up with a friend,
so I'm okay now. Bye!
What?
BLURRY
Does she know them?
Maybe not.
SCURRYING AWAY
High schoolers these days are scary.
Ain't that right.
Thank you so much.
Huh? I didn't do anything, did I?
Didn't you know them?
They came up to me out of nowhere.
You're so popular.
- It's not like that.
- What?
I mean,
what you saw wasn't like that.
Their vibe was that nothing else mattered
as long as they were having a good time.
Rather, they were looking down on me,
so it's not a situation
I can be happy about. So…
Hold on, why am I defending myself?
I should just play it off.
He's gonna get weirded out.
Should I have punched them?
No, you don't need to take it that far.
Are you sure?
Actually, I'm sorry. It's like
I used you to get away from them.
Why are you apologizing?
It's totally fine.
I wouldn't get upset
over something like this.
Do you live around here, Himuro?
No. I wanted to go
to the community center.
What? That's where I was going too.
Then, why don't we walk together?
Extracurricular activities will be on hold
during the exam preparation period…
- HR is going on forever!
- …so your daily routine may be disrupted.
Koyun, sorry I'm making you wait!
Say…
I'd like to know your name, please.
Right. I never told you my name.
My bad.
You can just call me Yota.
He only gave me his first name.
I WANTED TO KNOW HIS LAST NAME
It's a pleasure to meet you, Himuro.
Sorry.
My last name's actually Hikawa,
not Himuro.
No way! Sorry.
You should've told me sooner.
How much longer is it to get
to the community center?
I'm terrible with maps.
We'll be there in about five minutes.
Five minutes.
Can we keep
the conversation going for that long?
Hikawa, are you good friends with Miki?
We're childhood friends.
We live close, and we went to the same
elementary and middle school.
Is that so?
We went to the same cram school
in middle school.
What?
They've been friends since middle school?
Does that mean he knows the real Miki?
Now Miki.
You know, Miki,
I liked her much better
the way she used to be.
Me too.
Right?
Honestly, I want to tell everyone
what she's really like.
Seriously, what a waste.
No matter what you're like,
some people will want to stick by you.
You've gotta be kidding.
Hold on, isn't that Yota?
You're right.
But wait. That girl next to him, she's…
What?
MEITEN COMMUNITY CENTER
Here's your seat, Miki.
Thanks.
What the… What kind of pairing is this?
What kind…
Great question.
What?
Hey, I'm the one asking.
Sorry.
Geez! You guys surprised me!
Why didn't you give me a heads up?
I told her not to say anything.
I told her, "Let's surprise Miki!"
You too, Koyun.
Why'd you go along with it?
More importantly,
didn't you punch the jerks who hit on her?
No. Hikawa didn't want me to.
There's no need to go that far.
What?
Are you taking the same train?
I'll walk you to the station.
Thanks!
Yota, do you go to that study room often?
Yeah.
My younger brother and sister
are still little.
It's too noisy at home.
Right. How old are they again?
They're both three years old.
They're twins.
HIS MOM IS SUCH A TROOPER…
That's quite an age gap.
It's partly because
of the toddlers at home,
but I can focus better at the study room.
I feel you. I didn't check my phone today!
I didn't even have space to fool around.
Don't fool around.
Give me a minute.
I need some sugar to recharge
after all the studying I did.
Great idea. I'll grab a drink too.
He's taller than the vending machine.
It must be nice.
I wish I was born that way.
Take your pick, you two.
You don't mind?
I know you want the red bean soup, Miki.
You know me well.
Thanks, Yota.
I'll cover you next time.
Oh, my gosh! Why?
You used a bill, so how'd you
manage to scatter coins everywhere?
My bad.
What do you want to drink, Hikawa?
Me?
I FEEL BAD - SHAKE SHAKE
I…
Here, Miki. You can pick for her.
Leave it to me.
How about a warm corn soup for Koyun?
But I'm craving red bean soup,
so red bean soup it is!
What the heck?
Well, I want her to drink the same thing
so we can both say it's tasty.
You're so selfish.
They really do get along.
RED BEAN SOUP
Like I said earlier,
we went to the same cram school.
Miki, Minato, and I were always together.
Oh, yeah. We used to
eat and talk after cram school.
Mina… You mean Amamiya.
Hold on, Koyun, you know Minato too?
No, not really.
STRETCH
Don't tell me he picked on you again.
Again?
You poor thing.
You can just ignore him.
Yota, do you not get along with Amamiya?
I'm just kidding.
Koyun, Yota and Minato.
Hikawa, do people around you
call you Koyun?
PEOPLE RARELY CALL HER BY NAME
No, only Miki does.
- Koyun.
- Yes?
It's a good nickname.
Right?
Why are you smug about it?
I told you, you can be casual with me.
I don't like people being overly formal.
- No more talking so politely.
- What?
I get it.
I also feel more comfortable
when people are casual.
Is that how it is?
Thank you!
Yota, will you be
at the study room tomorrow too?
Yeah. I'll be there.
Then, see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
'Til tomorrow.
Koyuki Hikawa.
Huh, was there a girl like that?
I think she's Hikawa from Class 2.
Word is, she's always grouchy
and doesn't fit in with her class.
I thought Class 2 was pretty quiet.
Maybe it's more that she can't find
anyone she can relate to.
Since then, I kept following her
with my eyes every time we crossed paths.
She's by herself again.
STRETCH
I always thought,
"What a p…"
INCOMING CALL
NINE AUDIO
Sorry, Minato.
Can we meet right now?
There's something I want to talk about.
Okay. I'll come out.
What's this out of the blue?
You must be cold.
ROYAL MILK TEA
I want to break up.
What makes you say that?
I can't trust you.
You could chalk it up to kindness,
but you never liked me to begin with,
did you, Minato?
I can tell you're not into me.
Did I do something
that made you feel lonely?
Don't respond
to everything with questions.
You always do that.
I want to know how you really feel.
You know what, Minato?
You really don't have a sense of self.
I'm home.
Were you out, Minato?
Was it something urgent?
No.
It was nothing, really.
It's gonna be fine, Amamiya.
It must be rough.
Hey, I just got dumped.
Why don't you comfort me a little?
Well, how many times is it now?
It's starting to be funny.
Though, I'm sure you'll have
a new girlfriend in no time. Darn it, you!
Amamiya, you broke up? Again?
Yup.
She called me out when I was studying
last night. Then she broke up with me.
That's rough.
For some reason, I always get dumped.
Why do you think that is?
WE LET OUR GUARD DOWN,
AND THIS AGAIN - THUMP THUMP
Fujita! Don't let him trick you.
Don't hold eye contact
for longer than three seconds!
Okay.
- I'll hold him down. Now, go!
- Morning… Huh?
Minato, what'd you do this time? Sheesh.
I haven't done a thing. Why do you
always assume I've done something wrong?
Speaking of…
The cafeteria has a lot more options
if you get there early.
- Hey, Yota.
- Yeah?
Weren't you walking home
with Hikawa yesterday?
I'm sure he'd say…
It's not like that!
It's a misunderstanding!
You saw us.
What?
We happened to run into each other,
then decided to walk together.
Of course, yeah.
After all, you're…
NURSE'S OFFICE
Hey, Hikawa. Hello.
Why are you at the nurse's office?
Are you hurt?
No.
What's going on?
Yota.
"Yota"?
Koyun.
"Koyun"?
Are you feeling sick? Are you okay?
I just came to warm up by the heater.
What? Is it even that cold today?
It is, actually.
It's down to nine degrees Celsius.
You're wearing your contacts today?
- She won't even glance at me.
- Yup, totally. Wanna look at them?
- Not really.
- Hey, Hikawa.
SCHOOL NURSE - NORIKO
You're letting the cold air in.
If you're done, then leave.
Shoo, shoo.
We got in trouble.
Noriko's always like that.
Is your next class on the fourth floor?
We're going upstairs too.
No…
I meant to stop by my locker.
It's on the first floor.
Okay.
Well, then…
SCUTTLING AWAY
See you later.
"See you later"?
They happened
to run into each other, right?
Another productive night down!
But there are still concepts
I'm not quite grasping.
Sometimes, I want to talk while studying.
What if we study together in my classroom
after school tomorrow?
I'll help you with what I can.
Are you sure?
I'm counting on you, Yota-sensei!
It's no biggie--
Sensei! I heard a loud thud!
Ouch.
Hey! Does your head hurt?
Well, I'm always bumping
my head into things.
Yota's classroom…
seems noisy.
- It'll be fine.
- What?
The rambunctious ones
take off as soon as the bell rings.
True that.
- He read my mind. I'm embarrassed.
- Koyun's not good with that kinda vibe.
I'M ALL FOR IT THOUGH
CHUCKLE
SEAT FOR ONE
Rock, paper, scissors.
Please, go ahead.
You can take the seat.
PUBLIC FACE
Don't mind us.
We're getting off at the next stop.
What?
Please use the stairs in the center
of the platform to transfer between lines.
- The doors on platform three are closing.
- Quick! Shoot, shoot!
We made it.
Why'd you lie? Just give him the seat.
I got embarrassed.
FOGGY
Shoot, the glass fogs up
when I get close to it.
Now I'm laughing too.
Once the exams are over,
I'm signing up for more shifts at work.
We won't be able to go home together,
but stop by my restaurant sometime, Koyun.
THEY TEND TO TALK A LITTLE MORE
BEFORE THEY SAY GOODBYE
You've never been before.
I'll give you an extra serving of smiles.
Stylish burger!
It's kinda intimidating
to eat there by myself.
I'M A HIGH SCHOOLER
Spending over 1,000 yen on a burger
takes some nerve.
I'll talk to the manager,
he'll hook you up with a discount.
I've got you covered.
MANAGER
If you don't want to come alone,
just bring Yota.
He's got his club activities.
See ya.
See you tomorrow.
The laundry.
Was I smiling?
Today was so much fun.
I can't help but feel giddy
about what tomorrow might bring.
I'm better off on my own.
This is fun.
I'd rather not get involved.
I want to talk to them again.
Why can't they leave me alone?
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
No part of me is fake, but…
they contradict each other.
What do I really want to do?
I don't understand my own feelings.
GRADE 1 CLASS 6
Sneaking in.
Koyun! Come on in.
Pardon me.
Miki says she's running late.
She pinged me too.
Class 5 has the tendency to drag out HR.
Why don't we make a group chat?
Good idea.
Minato.
Are you two dating?
No. You've got the wrong idea.
Miki will be joining us shortly.
Miki? What's up with your friend group?
RATTLE
Minato, why are you here?
What, am I not supposed to be?
Not at all.
Miki is being herself.
FUNDAMENTALS OF PHYSICS
What's this? Is this a study group?
Bingo.
How fun.
Let me join too.
What?
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter